I'd like to begin by addressing the heinous attack
On the United States capitol
Like all Americans I am outraged by the violence
Lawlessness and Mayhem
I immediately deploy the National Guard
And federal law enforcement
To secure the building
And expel The Intruders
America is and must always be a nation of law
An order
The demonstrators who infiltrated the capital
Have defiled the seat of American democracy
To those who engage in the acts of violence and destruction
You do not represent our cut
And to those who broke the law
You will pay
We have just been through an intense election
And emotions are high
But now tempers must be cooled
AECOM
Restore
We must get on with the business of America
My campaign vigorously pursued every legal Avenue
Chicken test
The election results
My only goal was to ensure the Integrity of the vote
In so doing I was fighting to defend
American
I continue to strongly believe that we must reform our election laws
To verify the identity and eligibility
Hubbell Motors
And to ensure our faith
And confidence
That's it all future elections
Now Congress has certified the results
A new Administration will be inaugurated on January 20th
My focus now turns to ensuring a smooth orderly and seamless transition of power
This moment calls for healing and Reconciliation
2020 has been a challenging time for up
A menacing pandemic has upended the lives of our city
Isolated minions in their homes
Damage our economy
Inflame countless lives
Defeating this pandemic and rebuilding the greatest economy on Earth
Will require all of us working together
It will require A Renewed emphasis on the
Civic values of patriotism
Faith charity community and family
We must Revitalize the sacred bonds of love and loyalty that bind us together
As one National family
To the citizens of our country serving as your president has been
The honor of my life
And to all of my wonderful supporters
I know you are disappointed
But I also want you to know
That our Incredible Journey
Is only just beginning
Thank you God bless you
And God bless America